# Aníbal VR





## **Full Stack Web Developer**

#### **SUMMARY**

A self-motivated, fast leaner and hard working person, I love web development and learning new technologies. My focus is bringing an awesome user experience into all my projects. Experienced with digital marketing, web and android development.

#### **SKILLS**

## **Front-End Technologies**

- o React
- React Hooks
- o Redux
- o Responsive CSS3
- Sass
- Styled Components
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Material UI

## **Back-end Technologies**

- NodeJS
- o ExpressJS
- o PHP
- o MongoDB
- Mongoose
- o MVC Pattern
- o RESTful APIs

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Freelance – Full Stack Developer

#### 2014- Present

- Creating UI experiences to businesses in Chile/Santiago, focused on delivering high quality products aimed towards converting visitors.
- Creating high quality apps and websites.
- Writing clean, readable and modular code using best practices and programming patterns such as MVC and BEM.
- o Managing content, SEO and Digital Marketing for clients (Google Ads)

West World Games – Freelance Game Developer | Publisher

Designed and Developed different games using

#### 2017-2018

- Developed and design apps for Android
- Published application in the PlayStore
- Design images and UI/UX
- o Developed Google Ads campaigns.
- Worked with C# and Unity

Visit: https://avr00.github.io/my\_portfolio/

Lobby PMS – Front End Engineer

2015 - 2016

- Presents prototypes to CEO and Stakeholders.
- Leads design direction for a suite of applications
- o Developed highly robust Front-End products that connect to RESTful Microservices.

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

## Headnews – React / Redux / Redux Thunk / Axios / Newsapi

React application that renders the most important news from different countries and languages.

Visit Project: <a href="https://jolly-hypatia-445f35.netlify.com/us/general">https://jolly-hypatia-445f35.netlify.com/us/general</a>

## My Notes - React / Axios / Material-UI / MongoDB / NodeJS / ExpressJS / Heroku

Application to take notes it was made using the MVC pattern and the MERN Stack.

Visit Project: <a href="https://my-notes-mern.herokuapp.com/">https://my-notes-mern.herokuapp.com/</a>

## React Password Generator – React / Sass

React application that allows you to create strong password for best security with a beautiful UI

Visit Project: <a href="https://festive-nightingale-d10ab1.netlify.com/">https://festive-nightingale-d10ab1.netlify.com/</a>

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration Specialized in Marketing**

Technological University of Chile INACAP (2012-2016)

#### **Front-End Libraries Certificate**

freeCodeCamp (2016)

## **Responsive Web Design Certificate**

freeCodeCamp (2016)